http://www.eac.edu/privacy.shtm

State Authorization
Is Online Learning for You?
Housing
On- or Off-campus?
Information Collected by EAC
It is EAC’s policy not to collect personal information about you when you visit our web site unless you choose to make such information available to us.
When you visit our web site, our web servers automatically recognize only the Internet domain and IP address from which you accessed our web site. This information does not result in the identification of your personal email address or other personal information.
In addition, we gather information regarding the volume and timing of access to our web site by collecting information on the date, time and web site pages accessed by visitors to the web site. We do this so we can improve the content of our web site and this information is not shared with other organizations. Again, only aggregate information is collected and individual visitors' personal information is not identified.
Alternatives to Web Site Transactions
EAC web sites provide access to information and services for students, employees and members of the community. If you prefer not to provide any information to the College online, you may cancel the transaction and contact the administrative unit responsible for the service to learn about available options for conducting business in person, by mail or by telephone.
Disclosure of Information
If you choose to share personal information with us by sending us a message, or filling out an electronic form with personal information we will use the information only for the purposes you authorized or in support of college-sponsored programs.
If we are required to disclose information about you by law, we will make every effort to notify you of the disclosure in advance if such notification is not legally prohibited.
Links to External Sites
Eastern Arizona College web pages may provide links to external web sites or resources. Web sites that are not owned or managed by EAC are not bound by the College's online privacy policy; they may have their own policies or none at all. Often you can tell you are leaving an Eastern Arizona College web site by noting the URL of the destination site.
©2019
About EAC
Frequently Asked Questions
Thatcher and Safford Area
Thatcher Campus Map
Directions to Campus
Discovery Park Campus
President's Welcome
Documents linked from this page may require the Adobe Acrobat Reader
